let quiz_json = 
{
	"problems": [
		{
			"question": "1) The capital of Uzbekistan is ...",
			"choices": {
				"0": "Dusanbe",
				"1": "Taskent",
				"2": "Ulan Bator",
				"3": "Australia"	
			},
			"answer": "Taskent"
		},
		{
			"question": "2) The capital of Madagascar is ...",
			"choices": {
				"0": "New Delhi",
				"1": "Beijing",
				"2": "Antananarivo",
				"3": "New Kenya"
			},
			"answer": "Antananarivo"				
		},
		{
			"question": "3) The capital of Canada is ...",
			"choices": {
				"0": "Montreal",
				"1": "Quebec",
				"2": "Ottawa"	
			},
			"answer": "Ottawa"
		},
		{
			"question": "4) Whos capital is Kabul",
			"choices": {
				"0": "Afganistan",
				"1": "Turkmenistan"
			},
			"answer": "Afganistan"			
		},
		{
			"question": "5) The capital of Algeria is ...",
			"choices": {
				"0": "Alger",
				"1": "Libia",
				"2": "Cape Town",
				"3": "Cairo"	
			},
			"answer": "Alger"		
		},
		{
			"question": "6) The capital of Kirgiztan is ...",
			"choices": {
				"0": "Biskek",
				"1": "Bifshteks",
				"2": "Hamburger",
				"3": "Cheeseburger",
				"4": "Cartoshka fry"	
			},
			"answer": "Biskek"		
		},
		{
			"question": "7) The capital of Estonia is ...",
			"choices": {
				"0": "Vilnius",
				"1": "Talinn",
				"2": "Riga",
				"3": "Villnius"	
			},
			"answer": "Talinn"		
		},
		{
			"question": "8) The capital of Switzerland is ...",
			"choices": {
				"0": "Berna",
				"1": "Zurich",
				"2": "Genova",
				"3": "Sweden"	
			},
			"answer": "Berna"		
		},
		{
			"question": "9) The capital of Siria is ...",
			"choices": {
				"0": "Turkish",
				"1": "Damasc",
				"2": "Paris",
				"3": "Allah Akbar"	
			},
			"answer": "Damasc"		
		},
		{
			"question": "10) The capital of JavaScript:",
			"choices": {
				"0": "EcmaScript",
				"1": "Java",
				"2": "Allied",
				"3": "Stupid question"	
			},
			"answer": "Stupid question"			
		}
	]
};